[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Idaho is one of many states divided by two different time zones. Which part of the state is in the Pacific time zone?", "correct_answer": "Northern", "incorrect_answers": ["Southern", "Western", "Eastern"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1931, Fritz Lang directed this great movie about the lower level criminals of Germany and their world.", "correct_answer": "M", "incorrect_answers": ["Z", "Breathless", "Underground"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was Brian De Palmas movie Scarface released?", "correct_answer": "1983", "incorrect_answers": ["1978", "1988", "1980"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is used to refer to the infant koala, as well as to any other baby marsupial?", "correct_answer": "Joey", "incorrect_answers": ["Jerry", "Jimmy", "Jelly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these methods is used in tongue splitting, an example of extreme body modification?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Using a scalpel", "Using a surgical laser", "Tightening of a nylon bind around a tongue piercing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do fire ants, a type of venomous ants, introduce their venom?", "correct_answer": "Through stinging", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Through biting", "Through biting and then spraying the wound with venom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other common name is used for the New Caledonian bumpy gecko, a reptile found only on the southern end of the island of New Caledonia?", "correct_answer": "Gargoyle gecko", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Devil gecko", "Horny gecko"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of these James Bond movies was not released during the 80s.", "correct_answer": "Moonraker", "incorrect_answers": ["A View to a Kill", "Octopussy", "For Your Eyes Only"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the fourth-largest island in the world, and it is home to 5% of the plant and animal species on the planet.", "correct_answer": "Madagascar", "incorrect_answers": ["Jamaica", "Tasmania", "Cuba"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is located on the end of every arm of a starfish?", "correct_answer": "Eye", "incorrect_answers": ["Ear", "Whisker", "Mouth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which family of performers and musicians contributed the most to the Top 100 AFI films?", "correct_answer": "The Coppolas", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fondas", "The Hustons", "The Douglases"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress turned down the role of Nurse Ratched in the 1975 movie One Flew Over the Cuckoos Nest?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Geraldine Page", "Jane Fonda", "Angela Lansbury"]}]